pickensplan.com 2011-02-15

# PickensPlan: Privacy

**We respect your privacy. We will never sell or trade your email address or any other personal information to other organizations or companies.**

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
This Privacy Statement applies to the PickensPlan.com website and governs data collection and usage. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. PickensPlan.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by PickensPlan.com. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by PickensPlan.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PickensPlan.com website. PickensPlan.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment.

**Use of your Personal Information**

PickensPlan.com collects and uses your personal information to operate our website and deliver the services you have requested. PickensPlan.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other opportunities or services available from PickensPlan.com. PickensPlan.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

PickensPlan.com does not sell, rent or lease lists to third parties. PickensPlan.com may, from time to time, contact you about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to a third party. While we may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries, all such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to PickensPlan.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

PickensPlan.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from our website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. PickensPlan.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the PickensPlan.com and PickensPlan.com family of websites. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through PickensPlan.com public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

The PickensPlan.com website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PickensPlan.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PickensPlan.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PickensPlan.com, or the public.

PickensPlan.com abides by the standards set forth in the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). PickensPlan.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 and is not intended to solicit such information from children younger than 13.

**Changes to this Statement**  
PickensPlan.com may occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect user feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how PickensPlan.com is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
PickensPlan.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that PickensPlan.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

**Use of Cookies**  
The PickensPlan.com website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize PickensPlan.com pages, or register with the PickensPlan.com website or services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as email addresses, postal or shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PickensPlan.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PickensPlan.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PickensPlan.com web services or websites you visit.
